[{"question": "What is the data type of (1)?", "options": ["A.  Tuple", "B.  Integer", "C. List", "D.  Both tuple and integer"], "answer": "B.  Integer"}, {"question": "If a=(1,2,3,4), a[1:-1] is _________", "options": ["A. Error, tuple slicing doesn\u2019t exist", "B. [2,3]", "C. (2,3,4)", "D. (2,3)"], "answer": "D. (2,3)"}, {"question": "What type of data is: a=[(1,1),(2,4),(3,9)]?", "options": ["A. Array of tuples", "B. List of tuples", "C. Tuples of lists", "D. Invalid type"], "answer": "B. List of tuples"}, {"question": "Which of the following is a Python tuple?", "options": ["A.  [1, 2, 3]", "B. (1, 2, 3)", "C. {1, 2, 3}", "D. {}"], "answer": "B. (1, 2, 3)"}, {"question": "Suppose t = (1, 2, 4, 3), which of the following is incorrect?", "options": ["A. print(t[3])", "B. t[3] = 45", "C. print(max(t))", "D. print(len(t))"], "answer": "B. t[3] = 45"}, {"question": "Which of these about a set is not true?", "options": ["A. Mutable data type", "B. Allows duplicate values", "C. Data type with unordered values", "D. Immutable data type"], "answer": "D. Immutable data type"}, {"question": "Which of the following is not the correct syntax for creating a set?", "options": ["A. set([[1,2],[3,4]])", "B. set([1,2,2,3,4])", "C. set((1,2,3,4))", "D. {1,2,3,4}"], "answer": "A. set([[1,2],[3,4]])"}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is used to create an empty set?", "options": ["A. { }", "B. set()", "C. [ ]", "D. ( )"], "answer": "B. set()"}, {"question": "If a={5,6,7,8}, which of the following statements is false?", "options": ["A. print(len(a))", "B. print(min(a))", "C. a.remove(5)", "D. a[2]=45"], "answer": "D. a[2]=45"}, {"question": "If a={5,6,7}, what happens when a.add(5) is executed?", "options": ["A. a={5,5,6,7}", "B. a={5,6,7}", "C. Error as there is no add function for set data type", "D. Error as 5 already exists in the set"], "answer": "B. a={5,6,7}"}, {"question": "Which of these about a frozenset is not true?", "options": ["A. Mutable data type", "B. Allows duplicate values", "C. Data type with unordered values", "D.  Immutable data type"], "answer": "A. Mutable data type"}, {"question": "Which of the following lines of code will result in an error?", "options": ["A. s={abs}", "B. s={4, \u2018abc\u2019, (1,2)}", "C. s={2, 2.2, 3, \u2018xyz\u2019}", "D. s={san}"], "answer": "D. s={san}"}, {"question": "print(1)", "options": ["A 1", "B 0", "C 2", "D 4"], "answer": "A 1"}, {"question": "assd", "options": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "answer": "A"}]
